Roy Quilor

Designer

Introduction

Hi, I'm a self taught designer who builds sites in CSS and HTML from Hertford UK.

After graduating in 2003, I became a freelancer for two years, worked with agencies and my own clients. Then worked full time in software company for five years creating digital asset management systems.

Took some time out to be with my daughter and work on side projects. Worked at a startup as a contractor to get experience on React JS.

Contact

Email: roy@quilor.com

Web: quilor.com Twitter: @royquilor Github: royquilor

Education

University of Westminster, BSC, Multimedia Computing, 2001–2003.

Hammersmith & West London College HND Multimedia Computing, 1999–2001.

Skills

Design with a focus on web keeping it simple. Front-end development with a focus on CSS, HTML and JS.

Tools

Terminal, Atom, Git, Slack, Trello, Google Hangouts, Skype, Jira, Photoshop, Sketch

Experience

Founder

Awwesome

2014-Present

Side projects, two client wordpress sites for an estate agent and property investor.

Interaction Designer

Nift

2016-2017

Worked with Developers on React components. Create prototypes and static landing pages with Tachyons.

Senior Designer North Plains Systems

2009-2014

Worked on digital asset management systems for Diageo, Distell, Fox Sports Asia, Lowe, Nokia, Nestlé, Shell, Virgin Holidays. Mockups, prototype designs and build with HTML & CSS to hand off to developers.

Web Designer

Freelance

2007-2009

Design projects with agencies TLC Marketing and Winona eSolutions.

Intern

Xeuku Ltd

2006-2007

Assisted in the management and production of graphic presentations. Learned graphic design.